Hello,
hello friends, so in today's video I
welcome you all very much, so
in this video I will give a description about a
company in the insurance sector,
and in that
one of its own promoters and its company is
selling two of its honey here, so
let's go properly on that statement, so
friends, that company is ICICI
Lombard General Insurance, the quantity has been
reduced from the ICICI group, the company
is almost here today, there has been a
decline of about 100 third party here
and friends, if you
look here for 5 days, then there is a decline of about 1 percent
and in 1 month this company is
running under a lot of pressure and in six months
it has given a return of 9 percent,
but friends, these are very slow moving
companies, we will see the medium maximum chart
pattern, it has
given a return of about 1.8 percent here
and this company is not a small company, it is a
company associated with the SSC group, so we will go over this company,
friends, here you can see
ICICI Lombard General Insurance, so
friends, this is a financial service  By industry
type, you can see the financial
services it provides and
what are its products, you
can see here general insurance,
health insurance, health insurance,
travel insurance, friends,
how does the company do all this,
so friends, this company has been in the forefront for a long time
and friends, it has been
running its business in the market for a long time,
so friends, their promoter is one of them, his name is
ICICI and
his name is AB Cell, so friends, it is a
foreign company, so
first let me tell you about this company, after that we will
come to this,
friends, you can see this,
friends, well, this company
is a multinational insurance company of foreign brands, friends, friends, this is
its investment, ICICI
Lombard General Insurance, you
can see it, this is their headquarters, so
friends, it is also a pension service provider, it is
a company and friends, it also works,
its product you can see here is
life, it does property currency,
so  Friends, in this SSC 2011
insurance,
friends, this company has a profit of 3.5%.
This company has a stock.
So friends, this exhibition promoter is
criticizing the license and the security of the Central Insurance Company here for selling 3.5%. Sir, so
friends, you
can see here that the block deal file number is
General Insurance Company which was launched in
October. So friends, this block deal has happened yesterday. So
friends, this
company is selling here by making a profit of 3.57%.
These anchors are about 175 processed.
Friends, this company's stock is
about 175, they are selling them from the road for a
long time and that
price is 14972 5276. The
remaining price is 175 crores. The deal is being done at this price. So
friends, here it is
estimated to be Rs. 526 26 crores. Friends,
if you can see here,
its value is written as estimated here.  The test match test
price is 2626, wait, it
could be for yesterday, so
friends, he is the Finance Minister, so
friends, he is selling shares of such a company,
so why is he saving money,
we do not know, but from this we will know
about such a number General Insurance company, so
there the promoter, by the way, here again
we will discuss whether there is any problem in the company or not, we will discuss here, profit
and loss statement, balance and all this, so
here you can see the
market capital, the market cap,
friends, you can see here, it is
7500, friends, do this,
this is a class third step company, you can
see here, so friends, you can see its copy from the back, it
is 61.91 and you
can see the face value is ₹10,
so friends, here you will see the profit and loss
statement of such numbers General
Insurance, you can see here,
from 2010 to 2021 we have Boota,
forget it first and friends,
now we will see, friends, here you
can see, now we will see its net
Profit 211 you have ours, we have such love but
general insurance profit here
friends, since 2010 you can see here
its net profit has continuously
increased, so it has increased by approximately 100,
200 crores or 200 crores on the basis of glue,
here it has increased by one and a half or so you
can see this here, right now in 2021 its net profit is
1463,
2001, 473 crores, here its net
profit is
9th, 10th, you can see last year
its net profit was Vallabh twelve hundred
crores and hence the net profit of this share is
1470 crores, so friends, this is
its net profit increased
here, now if we look,
you can also see the net profit growth, in tension the red
button, at the Anwar Ali rate of 20%, the
net profit of this company is increasing,
so friends, now we have set its balance and
come up, friends you can see here
March number  From 17 to March 21, its
balance sheet has data, although here you
can see its share capital and
recharge plan, shareholder Pandey, here
friends, we will always consider things less, you
can see Pimple Sir Plus, you are continuously increasing,
its
recharge is there
and friends, if you
see the cooling Varun of this company here, then Varun is also around
4.5 crores, so it is a long term category, so
friends, continuously drinking on this company,
in five years,
4.5 crores, whatever happens here on this
and friends, see the stump color, you have nothing short
term growing on this company, the
balance sheet of this company is also good
and friends, you can also see the ad liability
here, that is also very good
and you can see what speed this company has,
either it is decreasing or sometimes it is
increasing, so friends, it is still late, does
this company have 227 crores in 2021, so
friends, now whatever data we have seen of this company,
then in April its was
quite good  There is a great opportunity here for the long term,
this company can oppose,
so friends, now we will look at it a little bit about computers,
so friends, now we can see its competitors,
you can see here that the
insurance sector is the finance and
investment
industry, so friends, at number one is
HDFC Life Insurance, at number two is
SBI Life Insurance, at number three
is ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance and at number 3434 is
ICICI Lombard, so friends, this company is a
very good company and
it comes at number four in its sector and
friends, you can see here that its
market capital is Rs 2500 crores and at
number one is HDFC Life
Insurance, its market capitalization is
more than Rs 1 lakh 4800 crores,
so friends, for speaking about stubble,
friends, the license for speaking about stubble,
suspended general insurance, is not a bad company now,
it is a company associated with the SSC group
and its maximum set one is
within such a company, it is
more than fifty one percent, so friends, here he has
his foreign investor  If I tweet once,
this company will not be bad, there is
no need for water, so friends,
this can be seen in six months, but this company is
definitely a little worried and friends, this can
become a pressure for a few days in the future, there can be
pressure on this company, but
with this we will meet in the next video
and thank you friends.